<resources>
    <string name="app_name">In Case of Emergency</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_circle_members_map">Map</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">log in</string>
    <string name="dontaccount">"Don't have an account? "</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="invitationcode">"Enter Invite code. if you want to join another circle"</string>
    <string name="join">join</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">Exit</string>
    <string name="dialog_message">Do you want to close this application</string>
    <string name="splashintro">"This app will help you to save your life In Case of Emergency by sending your Current Location and SMS to Police, Resque, Firebrigade and Family.
        This app is also the perfect GPS tracker for your family."</string>
    <string name="hide_code">- - - - - -</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last name</string>
    <string name="profile_email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="Fire">
1. Control flammables and ignition sources\n
2. Identify and control ignition sources\n
3. Before starting any hot work:\n
4. Confirm flammable material has been removed or isolated -\n
5. I obtain authorisation\n
6  Before starting hot work in a hazardous area I confirm  gas test has been completed\n
7. Gas will be monitored continually
    </string>
    <string name="Traffic">
   1. Drive at a safe speed!\n
2. Maintain distance between vehicles!\n
3. Do not cut off other vehicles!\n
4. Keep your eyes on the road!\n
5. Do not park on the expressway!\n
6. Do not drive on the shoulder!\n
7. Leave passing lanes open!\n
8. Expressways are one-way traffic!\n
9. Warn drivers behind you about traffic jams ahead of you!\n
10.Be aware of the angle of your headlight beams!\n
11.Do a thorough check and adjustment before departure!\n
</string>
    <string name="COVID">
1. Sneeze or cough?  Cover your nose and mouth with a tissue or use your elbow.\n
2. Wash your hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds.\n
3. Clean and disinfect surfaces around your home and work frequently.\n
4. Keep at least 6 feet between yourself and others if you must be in public.\n
5. Wear a cloth face covering over your mouth and nose when around others.\n
6. If your symptoms are severe, call to get medical attention immediately.
7. Persistent pain or pressure in the chest\n
8.Bluish lips or face\n
9. Trouble breathing
    </string>
    <string name="Safity">
1. Obtain authorisation before overriding or disabling safety controls\n
2. I understand and use safety critical equipment and procedures which apply to my task\n
3. l obtain authorisation before:\n
4. Disabling or overriding safety equipment\n
5. deviating from procedures\n
6. crossing a barrier\n
    </string>

    <string name="Authurization">
1. Work Authorisation\n
2. Work with a valid permit when required\n
3. I have confirmed if\n
4. permit is required\n
5. l am authorised to perform the work\n
6. I understand the permit\n
7. I have confirmed that hazards are controlled and it is safe to start\n
8. I stop and reassess if conditions change\n
    </string>

    <string name="Hight">
1. Protect yourself against a fall when working at height\n
2. l inspect my fall protection equipment before use\n
3. I secure tools and work materials to prevent dropped objects\n
4. I tie off 100% to approved anchor points while outside a protected area\
    </string>
    <string name="Earthquake">
1. Safety measures of earthquake\n
2. Check yourself and others for injuries.\n
3. Check water, gas, and electric lines for damage\n
4. Turn on the radio.\n
5. Stay out of damaged buildings.\n
6. Be careful around broken glass and debris.\n
7. careful of chimneys (they may fall on you).\n
8. Stay away from beaches.\n
9. Stay away from damaged areas.\n
    </string>
    <string name="CommonMistake">
         1.If glass in your home breaks it can be very dangerous to you and your family.\n
    2.Protect yourself first. Put on closed toed shoes and gloves if you have them.\n
    3.Very carefully pick up the large pieces of glass and dispose of them.\n
    4.It’s a good idea to wrap them in a thick paper product like newspaper or double wrapping it in \n
   5. Make sure the shards of glass are cleaned up. This task can be a bit trickier. \n
   6. Vacuum the area and surrounding area where the glass broke.\n


    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_circle_maps">Map</string>
</resources>
